<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eastern.nl - Performance Engineering done with passion</title>
    <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eastern.nl - Performance Engineering done with passion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.eastern.nl/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Techniques of my website</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/techniques-of-my-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/techniques-of-my-website/</guid>
      <description>Introduction My old website was 10 years old. Ofcourse I updated it a bit in the last years, but did not make a full responsive website. But, today it will change because I made a new one from scratch.
Hugo I was already thinking of building a new site a long time, but it is a big job to do if you want to start from scratch. Many opensource tooling websites are using GoHugo and that is the tool I wanted as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Mobile: +31 6 55 118 025
Email: erik@eastern.nl
Website: http://www.eastern.nl Mailing adresss Balustrade 20
7325 GP Apeldoorn
The Netherlands Other information IBAN: NL40RABO0393346072
BIC: RABONL2U
KvK: 08132235
VAT: NL002033564B54 Terms and conditions Nederland ICT 2014 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/references/</guid>
      <description>Ik heb Erik leren kennen tijdens mijn rol als projectmanager ‘Ontwikkeling werkplek infrastructuur’ bij het VUmc. Erik heeft een belangrijke rol gespeeld in ons skilled testteam, waarbij Erik verantwoordelijk was voor de uitvoering en, bij afwezigheid van de testmanager, de coördinatie van de testen. Erik heeft goede ICT infrastructurele kennis, en weet zijn kennis goed te combineren met collega’s. Erik is praktisch, heeft een gezonde drive voor kwaliteit, kan prioriteiten stellen en staat open voor veranderingen in planningen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:04:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>My name is Erik van Oost, living in Apeldoorn – The Netherlands and IT-freelancer since 2003. My passion for IT brings me to places where I work with much enjoyment for organizations who hire me.
I have been working in IT since 2000 and have done several functions. In the last 7 years I am specialized in the area of performance testing and engineering. I have gained a lot of experience with developing, programming and analyzing performance tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:04:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/services/</guid>
      <description>Performance testing We offer the complete journey to ensure an application has a correct performance. Starting with an intake, gather all the requirements and make a load model to run the test. Scripting the application in a proper tool like JMeter, LoadRunner and if needed extra scripting to support the test in Python, Bash, Rexx, PowerShell or other scripting languages.
Setup proper monitoring, the preferred tooling is Telegraf, Influx and Grafana but we are open to other tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VDI Performance Summit</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/vdi-performance-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/vdi-performance-summit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On 29th january I visited the VDI Performance Summit which was organized by LoginVSI. Login VSI provides performance insights for virtualized desktop environments such as Citrix XenApp, XenDesktop, Microsoft RDS and VMware Horizon View.
The summit was, of course, organized around the LoginVSI tool. In this blog post I will tell you the 5 quick takes of the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;images/vdi-performance-summit.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/vdi-performance-summit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&#34;images/i-love-a-good-performance.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/i-love-a-good-performance.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run and enable Microsoft App-V client on Windows 10 Anniversary Update</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/run-or-enable-microsoft-app-v-client-on-windows-10-anniversary-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/run-or-enable-microsoft-app-v-client-on-windows-10-anniversary-update/</guid>
      <description>What is the problem with App-V on Windows 10 Anniversary Update Microsoft released App-V as an add-on for Windows in the MDOP (Microsoft Desktop Optimization Pack). So I also run App-V to have some hands on experience with applications on my Windows 8.1 and later Windows 10 installation. Last week I upgraded to Windows 10 Anniversary Update 1607, and I run in to errors with App-V applications. My Total Commander session lost all the configuration settings, slow starting or even not starting App-V applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clock application with milliseconds</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/clock-application-with-milliseconds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 12:57:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/clock-application-with-milliseconds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The clock application with milliseconds which run always on top! This little tool is build to capture the exact time in case of an performance problem. With an extra tool for video recording it can help to record the screen of the user, and see the probably performance slowness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/clock.png&#34; alt=&#34;clock picture&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detailed logon information from Citrix Director</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/detailed-logon-information-from-citrix-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 12:57:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/detailed-logon-information-from-citrix-director/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-to-have-detailed-logon-information-from-citrix&#34;&gt;Why to have detailed logon information from Citrix?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes anyone is asking you, the performance is not what we like. Within a Citrix environment it is easy to get into the director to see the overview of the logon times.
By default Citrix Director gives the following information about the logon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;images/citrix-director.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/citrix-director.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplace and VDI test automation with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/workplace-and-vdi-test-automation-with-powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/workplace-and-vdi-test-automation-with-powershell/</guid>
      <description>Why to do test automation with PowerShell? I was involved in a project to implement a new Virtual Desktop Infrastructure (VDI) within a large company
To ensure the environment is stable and well-functioning all the time on the same way, I made a script to test the basic functionality of the virtual desktop image. The script also measures the time it takes to complete an action, so this can be used to set a baseline for performance measurement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount VMFS on Centos 7</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/mount-vmfs-centos-7-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 12:57:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/blog/mount-vmfs-centos-7-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-vmfs-on-centos-7&#34;&gt;Why VMFS on CentOS 7?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was running a VMware ESXi server since 4 years. In VMware ESXi the options for local storage are limited, especially when you like redundant storage. The option is to buy a Raid adapter. I decided to move to CentOS with ZFS storage.
Moving the VM’s to a Linux disk can be done by moving all the files to a NFS share, but an another option is to mount the VMFS filesystem. This is not natively available in Linux, but with fuse and vmfs-tools you can make it available. In this article I will describe how I did the installation and movement of the VM’s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
