<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Eastern.nl - Performance Engineering done with passion</title>
    <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Eastern.nl - Performance Engineering done with passion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Mobile: +31 6 55 118 025
Email: erik@eastern.nl
Website: http://www.eastern.nl Mailing adresss Balustrade 20
7325 GP Apeldoorn
The Netherlands Other information IBAN: NL40RABO0393346072
BIC: RABONL2U
KvK: 08132235
VAT: NL002033564B54 Terms and conditions Nederland ICT 2014 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/references/</guid>
      <description>Ik heb Erik leren kennen tijdens mijn rol als projectmanager ‘Ontwikkeling werkplek infrastructuur’ bij het VUmc. Erik heeft een belangrijke rol gespeeld in ons skilled testteam, waarbij Erik verantwoordelijk was voor de uitvoering en, bij afwezigheid van de testmanager, de coördinatie van de testen. Erik heeft goede ICT infrastructurele kennis, en weet zijn kennis goed te combineren met collega’s. Erik is praktisch, heeft een gezonde drive voor kwaliteit, kan prioriteiten stellen en staat open voor veranderingen in planningen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:04:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>My name is Erik van Oost, living in Apeldoorn – The Netherlands and IT-freelancer since 2003. My passion for IT brings me to places where I work with much enjoyment for organizations who hire me.
I have been working in IT since 2000 and have done several functions. In the last 7 years I am specialized in the area of performance testing and engineering. I have gained a lot of experience with developing, programming and analyzing performance tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:04:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eastern.nl/en/pages/services/</guid>
      <description>Performance testing We offer the complete journey to ensure an application has a correct performance. Starting with an intake, gather all the requirements and make a load model to run the test. Scripting the application in a proper tool like JMeter, LoadRunner and if needed extra scripting to support the test in Python, Bash, Rexx, PowerShell or other scripting languages.
Setup proper monitoring, the preferred tooling is Telegraf, Influx and Grafana but we are open to other tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
